Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 69, Folder: 26 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Editorial "For We Are The State", Publication (Box 69, Folder 26)
    By Fred C. Crowell, Jr. Reprinted by permission of The Insurance Field -- October 31. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, Folder: 27 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Political Dynamics of a Soviet Satellite, Publication (Box 69, Folder 27)
    By Richard F. Staar. This article is a chapter from a forthcoming book, Sovietizing a Captive Nation. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, Folder: 28 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: iabcnews vol. 6 no. 7, January 1977, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
    By International Association of Business Communicators. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: iabcnews vol. 6 no. 10, April 1977, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: iabcnews vol. 8 no. 2, August 1978, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: iabcnews vol. 8 no. 6, December 1978, Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: The International Association of Business Communicators reached two significant milestones today when it chartered its 100th chapter - and it is based in London, England., Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
    By International Association of Business Communicators. February 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Louis C. Williams, Jr., ABC executive vice president and general manager of the Chicago office of Harshe-Rotman & Druck, has been elected president of the International Association of Business Communicators for 1979-80., Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
    By International Association of Business Communicators. June 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: "Without Buas: A Guidebook for Nondiscriminatory Communication," published by the International Association of Business Communicators, won a 1979 Clarion Award presented by Women in Communications, Inc., Publication (Box 69, Folder 28)
    By International Association of Business Communicators. July 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 69, Folder: 29 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits Plan, IBM, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
    By International Business Machines. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: IBM Employees Health Association: Constitution, By-Laws, Rules, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Yesterday and today, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: International Business Machines Corporation Personnel Procedure: All Plants, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: IBM Accounting: Personnel and Employee Benefit Records, Publication (Box 69, Folder 29)
- Box: 69, Folder: 30 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Ortho-Rater Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Manager's Guide to Performance Planning,Counseling and Evaluation, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: The McKinsey Foundation Lectures, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
    By Thomas J. Watson, Jr.. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Teaching Suggestions For Instructors, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Curriculum For Apprentice Toolmakers, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: About Your Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: A Business and its Beliefs The ideas that helped build IBM, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
    By Thomas J Watson Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: About Your Company IBM Benefit Improvements, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: yesterday and today, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Employment Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: General Education Program Spring Term Supplement, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: General Education Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: Supplement to the 1948-49 General Education Bulletin, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: Employment of Handicapped Individuals, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: Endicott IBM School 1945 1946, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: General Educaton Program, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: About Your Company, Publication (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Box: 70, Folder: 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: International Harvester Company And It's Employes, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
    By International Correspondence Schools. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Harvester Policies For Harvester People, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Recommended Training Methods That Will Succeed in Your Plant, Publication (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Box: 70, Folder: 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade and Telecommunications: Recommendations of Users of Telegraph and Telephone Services, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    By International Chamber of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Maximum Employment in a Free Society, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    By International Chamber of Commerce. Resolution and Report Adopted by the Council of the International Chamber of Commerce at its 65th Meeting, Paris, France, December 3rd and 4th, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Proceedings of a Regular Meeting of the Board of Governors of the International Allied Printing Trades Association, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    By Woodruff Randolph. Held in Cincinnati, Ohio, October 2-3; 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: International Council of Industrial Editors Constitution, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    By International Council of Industrial Editors. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Oiling the Squeaks in Human Relations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    By John L. McCaffrey. Address before the Western Petroleum Refiners Association, San Antonio, Texas, March 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial and Government at the Grass Roots, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    By John L. McCaffrey. Address before the United States Conference of Mayors, Washington, DC, March 22, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Your Instructors - How Well Do They Teach?, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Intarnational Harvester Company, Bettendork Works - Bettendorf, Iowa, Welder Training School, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Box: 70, Folder: 4 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Harvester Industrial Council - International Harvester Company and subsidiary companies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. March 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Safety Rule Book for Industrial Truck and Tractor Operators, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. Fort Wayne Works. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Welcome to Harvester, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Unstoppable: The Story of the Harvester Strike (August 21 - November 15, 1952), Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: After Hour Training Courses Book 2, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Tractor Works After Hour Bulletin, Spring 1949, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Employes' Educational Program for The Season 1948-49, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Economics of Freedom, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Educational Opportunities in the Harvester Employe Education Program - West Pullman Works, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. To make available to all west pullman works employes the opportunity to attain or to continue their education in any field that interests them. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. December 23; To the Employes of International Harvester Company of New Jersey and Its Subsidiary Companies. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Application for Profit Sharing Certificates, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Draw-in Collet Chuck, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. Newspaper or magazine clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The following tables have been prepared to show how monthly payments of $1 and upwards will pay for Profit Sharing Certificates in amounts ranging from $50 to $1,000, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    By International Harvester Company. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Comparison of Weighted Average Wage Rates Paid By Fort Wayne Works Of International Harvester Company With Those Paid By Other Fort Wayne Companies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations and Labor Relations Discussion Guide for Sessions I to V, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Box: 70, Folder: 5 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employment Manual - Industrial Relations Department, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Box: 70, Folder: 6 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Selections from Skilled Trade and Affiliated Work Job Specifications of the International Harvester Company -- Occupational Rating Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    By International Harvester Company. Set of cards describing different positions' desirable specifications, tools used, etc., including blank spaces for "rate data". Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 7 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: You and Safety!, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Scriptographic Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Harvester Human Resource Handbook, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Developed to communicate essential information about the plans, policies and rprocedures currently applicable to non-managerial, non-unionized salaried employes of International Harvester. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The ABC's of Moving Things Safely!, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The ABC's of Water Safety, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Safety Handbook for Employes of IHH, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Mission Responsible: The responsibility for wearing safety equipment is YOURS!, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Agricultural Equipment Division Incentive Compensations Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Effective November 1, 1974; for Area Managers. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Harvester Savings and Investment Program for Eligible Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Supplement To Prospectus. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: C & T Employe Orientation Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Profile Sheet for Accountability Achievement, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: The ABC's of On-The-Job Safety: How to prevent Accidental Injury and Death, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Incentive Compensation Program: Branc Managers & Branch Sales Managers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Effective November 1, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Employes Savings and Extra Compensation Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. For International Harvester Company and Affiliated Compnies; Effective May 1, 1940; 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Salary Range Increase Guide, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Anatomy of A Salary Range, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: History and Development of International Harvester, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Tuition Refund Policy, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By Roy Richardson. To Managers of All US Operations, January 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. To Managers of All US Operations, September 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Tuition Refund Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. September 1st. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Employe Orientation Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Leader's Guide for Conducting The Performance Management Workshop, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Prepared by the Corporate Staff Manpower Development and Training Deparment. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The wise old Turk: Your best source for job-design ideas is probably already on your payroll; he knows how things were done before behavioral science took over, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By Frederick Herzberg. From Harvard Business Review, September-October 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Contributory Annuity Plan for Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. As amended and in effect on and after January 1, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. As amended and in effect on and after December 20, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Pension Regulations, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. January 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Benefit Plans for the Employes of International Harvester Company, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    By International Harvester Company. Revised issue of 9/1/1920. Organized 9/1/1908. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 8 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: General Office Approved Personnel Policies, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Box: 70, Folder: 9 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Demographic Trends in Higher Education: Collective Bargaining and Forced Unionism, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    By James T. Bennett; Manuel H. Johnson. Original Paper 20. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 10 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: L'Institut International Du Travail Temporaire, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
    By R. Blanpain. Item is in French; Flemish.
  - Item 2: International Conference on Temporary Work, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
    By International Institute for Temporary Work. April 28. Item is in Flemish; French; English.
  - Item 3: L'Institut International Du Travail Temporarire, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
    By International Institute for Temporary Work. objectifs, options fondamentals, cahiers, conference. Item is in French.
  - Item 4: Guidelines, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
    By International Institute for Temporary Work. Item is in Flemish; French; English.
  - Item 5: Reunion du Bureau, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
    By International Institute for Temporary Work. Item is in French.
- Box: 70, Folder: 11 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Activities, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
    By International Joint Conferenc Council of the Commercial and Periodical Branches Printing Industry. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 12 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The United States in the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    By Ethel M. Johnson. Reprinted with minor changes from Information Service for September 9, 1939, through the courtesy of the Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The ILO at Work, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    By International Labor Organization. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Labor Conference 1950, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Recommending Continued American Participation in the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The Communist Issue in the 38th International Labor Conference of the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    By William L. McGrath. Geneva, Switzerland. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Constitution Objects and Results, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    By International Labor Organization. Geneva, October. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Constitution of the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: American Emloyers and the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
    By International Labor Organization. Assessment of the value of United States business participation in the International Labor Organization and a propposed course of action for American employers respecting that agency. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 13 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Exploding Foibles and Fables in Internal Management, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By D. J. Stark. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Salaried Employee Benefits Summary, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Retiree Medical Plan - Hospital and Medical Care Plan for Employees of International Minerals & Chemical Corporation: A Certificate of Coverage, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: IMC's Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Complete Formal Plan Effective January 1, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: IMC's Retirement Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Summary of Formal Plan Effective February 1, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: IMC's Retiree Health Care Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Revised July, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: General Information: IMC Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Position Guide and Analysis, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Completion Instructions for Position Guide and Analysis, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Revised October 1974. Item is in English.
- Box: 70, Folder: 14 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Manitoba story: An exciting new chapter in the Romance of Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Romance of Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. Revised Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Exciting Story of Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Man and Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Group Medical Surgical Plan for the Employees of The International Nickel Company, Inc., Bayonne Works, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. January 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Accident and Sickness Insurance Plan for Hourly, Tonnage, and Piece Rate Employees of The International Nickel Company, Inc. Huntongton Works, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. May 1st. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Security Reserve Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    By International Minerals and Chemical Corporation. October 1st. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: International Nickel, as One of Canada's Major Mining Industries, Needs More Trained Men, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
    By International Nickel Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Career Oppurtunities with International Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Career Opportunities with INCO, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: The Romance Of Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Canadian Mining Journal, Publication (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Box: 70, Folder: 15 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: An Outline Of Ontario Health Insurance Your Health Care Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: International Nickel Major Medical Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Prescription Drug Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: International Nickel Major Dentistry Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    By International Nickel Co. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Long Term Disability Income Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Highlights of Special Leave Program for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Benefits Highlights, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: The Romance Of Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: INCO Process Research, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
    By J. Roy Gordon. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: This is International Nickel, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: The Nickel Industry In Canada, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: The International Nickel Company Of Canada, Limited Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Strike Report, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: To the Shareholders, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 23 Number 3 Mine and Market, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 23 Number 2 Spring, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 22 Number 12 Very Unexpected Visitor, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 23 Number 1 It's Trophy Time, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 22 Number 11 The Music Man, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: INCO TRIANGLE Volume 22 Number 10 "Okay, let 'er go!", Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: INCO NEWS Huntington Works, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: International Organisation Of Employers, Publication (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Box: 71, Folder: 1 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wage Incentive Manual, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    By Johns-Manville Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 71, Folder: 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Time Study Manual, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Box: 71, Folder: 3 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Johns-Manville Today History, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employee Counseling Service, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Hospitalization Surgical/ Medical And Major Medical Program, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Prescription Drugs, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Group Dental Program, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Voluntary Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Your Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Johns-Manville Handbooks, Manuals packet, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    By Johns-Manville Corporation. Plastic folder with original handbooks. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Salary Administrative Plan, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Work Planning, appraisal and review, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Work Planning, appraisal and review Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Letters Have you read your own lately?, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    By Johns-Manville Office of Relationships Training Department. Item is in English.
- Box: 71, Folder: 4 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Contact October 1962, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
    By John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co.. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Contact December 1962, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Contact Jan 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Contact Feb 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Contact March 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Contact May 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: June 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Contact September 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Contact October 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Contact Nov-Dec 1963, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Contact Jan 1964, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Contact Feb-Mar 1964, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Contact May 1964, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Contact March 1965, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Contact Feb 1965, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)